Okay, good.
- It's better than making multiple trips.
- Right.
Nice, you're doing well.
Watch your step.
STUMBLES
What is it?
Darn it, I stepped on poop!
- You stepped on poop?
- I stepped on poop!
I really stepped on it
You really did.
You didn't just step on it.
You rubbed it in, Zuha.
What you stepped on
must've come from that cow.
Right, the rubbed-in poop.
BACK WITH TABLES AND CHAIRS FOR THE PARTY
Put them down.
Good job.
Hold on.
CHECKING
Is this poop?
CHECKING AGAIN
AND AGAIN
Is it there?
Isn't that poop on your shoes?
SHE SHAKES IT OFF OUTSIDE
One, two, three.
Okay.
You're really smelling it?
SHE SMELLS IT TO CHECK
You did ballet for this?
No, it's just in case.
But I think this is dirt.
But I think I can smell it.
- Kazuha stepped on poop on the way back.
- What?
No, I didn't.
How do I prep these?
CHICKEN BREAST NAENGCHAE SALAD
I'll cut them into a size you want.
Cut them into long, thin strips.
Peel the cucumbers
and remove the seeds.
"Long, thin strips."
- Yes, I'd appreciate that.
- Okay.
You're pretty good.
You're quite a good cook now.
Well, at home…
THE SOUS-CHEF CAN COOK A BIT
I got sick of delivery food.
- Really?
- You don't cook?
I don't cook often.
Since delivery apps
are set up so well in Korea,
I don't end up cooking much.
Hold on.
You said to cut them long and thin.
What? That's not it.
That's not how you cut them.
You have to julienne them
into long strips.
- Julienne them?
- Yeah.
They're sweet.
CHOPPED INTO LITTLE PIECES
Hey, is this right?
- What?
- This.
No, you diced them.
I don't know how to julienne them.
I don't know either,
so I asked you to do it, but you…
Well, let's just do it this way.
Shouldn't they be cut long like this?
I'm not good at cutting.
Aren't they supposed to look like this?
And then, don't you chop them?
They're so thick. You'll lose a tooth.
How can we chew these?
Try one.
THE BIZARRE CUTTING DUO
They have to be crunchy though.
Make them a bit more…
What do you mean? Yours are thicker.
THICKLY SLICED AND DICED CARROTS
CHOPPED BELL PEPPERS
They're not coming out the way I wanted.
FLAT CUCUMBER PIECES
This looks like feed for cows.
THEY WERE SUPPOSED TO BE LONG AND THIN
I'll try to make the dressing.
MAKING THE SALAD DRESSING
I have no idea how this will turn out.
I don't know the ratio.
About this much.
BY FEEL
I didn't measure anything.
I just added them.
- I don't measure either.
- You just do it.
SAME COOKING PHILOSOPHY
I went by feel.
We should taste-test it.
It's mustard-based.
- Mustard-based?
- Yeah.
Isn't that a lot?
SLURPING
FULL OF ANTICIPATION
You try it.
It's not good?
It tastes like, "Do I have to eat this?"
Like, "Why?"
"Why did they have to make salad?"
It tastes like that.
THE REVIEW MAKES HER HUMBLE
It's not that good. What am I missing?
SEARCHING AGAIN
Let's add sugar.
Sugar?
- I'll put it in.
- Okay.
It needs to be sweet.
NERVOUS
- It's much better.
- It's okay?
- Yeah.
- Much better?
Much better.
- It is?
- Yeah.
- Isn't it better?
- This is it.
It's good.
I was worried about the dressing.
- It's good.
- They'll eat this, right?
- Yeah.
- It's not bad.
Salad takes a lot of work to make.
Shredding chicken breast takes so long.
- I'll put it in.
- Okay.
Put some in here too. Not all of it.
COMBINED
Time to mix it up.
- Yeah.
- I think it'll be fine.
It's good.
How is it?
The dressing tastes good now, right?
- It's good?
- Yeah.
It's delicious.
THE SALAD IS READY
But today,
you're helping me more than I expected.
Am I being helpful?
I couldn't have done this alone.
RELIABLE
Three tables for now.
THEY BEGIN ARRANGING TABLES BELOW
Okay.
I think we can use this as a table.
- Right? Yeah.
- Like this?
- It's for the food.
- That's a great idea.
I think it'll work.
I thought we were doing it like this.
Hey, that's a good idea.
You're right.
- Set it up.
- Good, right?
- They've never been used.
TABLE FOR FOOD
It's nice.
Let's make it flat.
This way, the food won't spill.
MAKING IT FLAT WITH A TRAY
It's awkward to have the inside showing.
LEAVING MUCH TO BE DESIRED
Should we add another layer?
It'd be okay if we hid it.
Let's…
LET'S COVER THE FRONT SIDE
Right.
The lettuce.
CABBAGE BLANKET APPEARS
Try covering the front.
- It'll look great.
- Totally.
Hold this.
LETTUCE TABLECLOTH
Great.
It looks good.
- It's Kian's B&B-esque.
- Yeah.
THIS IS KIAN'S B&B-ESQUE
I think it's good.
- Right?
- Yeah.
- Let's take what we brought…
- And unfold them?
NOW TO PLACE ALL THE SEATS
Let's wipe down the legs first.
Boss, do we have any rags?
- Rags?
- Yes.
RAGS TO CLEAN CHAIRS
Use one of mine over there.
But this isn't a rag. It's a towel.
BOSS'S TOWELS
I use towels as rags too.
What are you talking about?
- What are you…
- Use it.
- I can just wash it later.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
- Then, I'm going to write on it.
- "Rag."
- Go ahead.
I use towels as rags and vice versa.
You can just wash them.
He uses them as rags too?
MARKED TO AVOID CONFUSION
Write "rag" in Japanese for me.
"Rag"?
- "Sōkin"?
- Zōkin.
IN JAPANESE AS WELL
Gosh, this is…
That should do. Try setting one up.
Wherever you like.
Wherever I like?
Like an awards show.
- An awards show?
- Yeah.
I think we'll need
big chairs in the front.
AWARDS SHOW LAYOUT
Right in the front.
BIG CHAIRS IN THE FRONT
4 PEOPLE PER TABLE
There we go. Okay.
Is this good?
Good job.
- Where should we put this?
- Let's put beverages…
- Okay.
- …and food on this.
Okay, food and beverages.
Okay. Good job.
FOR REFRESHMENTS
It looks so good.
That's done.
SATISFIED WITH THE LAYOUT
Let's use these boxes then.
BOXES FOR DINING TABLES
If we turn them over and cover them…
- Right?
- There we go.
- It's a pizza.
- All set.
That's good.
PIZZA TABLE
It looks great.
- And an egg here.
- That looks good.
Egg.
EGG TABLE
It's nice. It looks good.
AND…
How about this?
Gosh, what a great idea.
After they finish their snacks,
they can play Go.
Nice. Let's put these on.
GO BOARD TRAY
EVEN A TABLE LAMP THAT SETS THE MOOD
Boss gave us such a difficult task to do.
But together,
we thought about how to make
the place feel different.
I wanted them to enjoy
Kian's incredible imagination
as much as possible.
The vibe is so different now.
Yeah, it's so nice.
Kian, what do you think?
Is this good enough?
You did a great job.
- Okay.
- We did it.
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED
Once the food's ready,
we'll be done in no time.
Only the pasta's left.
I'm pretty confident about it.
HOT PEPPER SAUCE TUNA PASTA
ADDING TUNA TO TOMATO SAUCE
- Once the sauce simmers, I'm done.
- Really?
Now, stir it. You have to stir it in.
We need to bring this down as is.
YEON-KOUNG'S HOT PEPPER SAUCE TUNA PASTA
The place looks nice.
- Right?
- Yeah.
I think it's perfect.
Now, the glasses.
We just need to rinse them.
LAST THING IS CLEANING WINE GLASSES
Gosh, we put in a lot of work.
- Maybe too much.
- Too much.
LUGE TEAM RETURNS AFTER TRIP
This will be our last time here now.
We're checking out tomorrow.
One, two, three.
- Nice.
- We're used to it now.
EASILY
- We're back, Mr. Kian.
- We're back.
Welcome back.
What's this?
It looks like a campground.
This is awesome.
They already sound excited.
See? The reaction's different.
- He's satisfied.
- He likes it.
He laughs like that when he's satisfied.
He's happy.
Things are going as planned.
He loves it.
Let's give it a try.
YOO-MIN, KOTARO,
SUNG-NAM, SEONG-JUN RETURN
Thank you.
- Hello.
This is amazing.
What's this?
EVERYONE'S BACK
This looks incredible.
Help yourselves to the food, everyone.
Yes, help yourselves.
Yes, you can serve yourselves.
LIKE AN AWARDS SHOW?
I'll scoop the pasta for you.
MAIN CHEF SERVES THE PASTA
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- You can have seconds.
- Okay.
- Taro gets a lot for his big appetite.
- Thank you.
This has tuna.
It's delicious.
Is the pasta okay? How is it?
It's good.
Is the pasta okay?
It's nice and rich.
This is good, Yeon-koung.
Try it.
SHE SITS DOWN LAST
AFTER CHECKING THEIR RESPONSES
Everyone, it's your last night,
so let's have a toast.
- Sure.
- All right.
The night is long, so take your time.
You can have some beer,
and I hope you enjoy your last night.
- Cheers!
- It's been a pleasure.
HAPPY KIAN'S B&B DAY IS OPEN
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
Hey, what do you think of this?
Compared to eating on the floor?
I love camping vibes.
- Okay. This vibe?
- So I love this atmosphere.
I love it.
PROUD
Are you going to sing today?
- Sing?
- No pressure.
NERVOUS
When do we start? At 8:00 p.m.?
Let's start at around 8:00 p.m.
KARAOKE OPENS AT 8:00 P.M.
MEANWHILE, AT ANOTHER TABLE
When did you start doing lu…
- Luge.
- Yes, luge.
Not that long ago. We started last year.
That's right.
They started last year,
and they're already on the national team.
That's amazing.
Want to see my run?
Yeah, show us.
This is the start.
It's so fast.
They're going so fast.
It looks pretty dangerous.
We do get injured often.
I bumped into a wall here
and got knocked off.
What?
Like this.
Athletes sure are different.
How did they even think of doing this?
But to become a member
of the national team
is a great honor.
- Right.
- It's a huge honor.
- How is the pasta?
- It's good.
I've never eaten this much pasta before.
- Really?
- Yes.
You don't have pasta often?
Only with my daughters.
Would you like some kimchi?
KIMCHI?
I wasn't thinking about it,
but now that you've mentioned it,
I'm craving kimchi.
I'll bring you some.
GETTING UP
PERSONAL SIDE DISH SERVICE
FROM MAIN CHEF
It's kimchi. Give it to Mr. Lee.
SEONG-JUN DELIVERS IT
Please enjoy.
He's been saying all day long,
"I want to hang out with Kazuha."
GASPING
Really? Let's talk.
Please sit.
SEONG-JUN JOINS
Did you have fun today?
We played "Would You Rather" too.
Let's play it now.
IT'S "WOULD YOU RATHER" TIME AGAIN
You can ask us questions.
- For you two?
- Yes.
LOOKING FORWARD TO IT
Something simple. You know, like…
A penniless
or in debt…
Park Bo-gum?
What?
So it's a "Would You Rather"
about your ideal romantic type?
SERIOUS
This is so funny.
- You're impossible, Mr. Lee.
- He is.
Right? Isn't he unbelievable?
Or with ten billion won…
You have to pick a good opponent.
I think Park Bo-gum would be better.
I can just pay off
the 10 billion for Bo-gum.
She's on a different level.
"I'll just earn the money."
Give us one more.
One more?
Under current circumstances,
you two switch your careers.
- You become Kazuha.
- Right, Kazuha.
And you take her career as a K-pop idol.
But your entire volleyball career is gone.
Gone?
And you become a volleyball player
who reigns as the world's best.
I become a volleyball player?
But ballet and everything else are gone.
- LE SSERAFIM's gone too.
- My gosh.
- Will you switch or not switch?
- Okay.
- Yes or no.
WORLD-CLASS VOLLEYBALL PLAYER
VS. GLOBAL GIRL GROUP
- Ready?
- Yes.
One, two, three.
Yes.
YES, NO
- Seriously?
- Yes.
GENUINELY SURPRISED
Hold on.
But why?
I want to be delicate and graceful.
You know…
That would suit you well.
I want to do this for once.
And give up your career?
- It's fine.
- No way.
I've already experienced this life.
- Come on. Really?
- So I know what it feels like.
But I don't know this life.
Why did you say no then?
Me? If I took on her career,
I'd have to keep walking that path.
I wasn't sure I could do that.
- To maintain that career?
- Yes.
I am curious though.
Right?
We decided earlier to do the dishes.
We'll go do them now.
Thank you so much.
DINNER COMES TO AN END
YEON-KOUNG AND SUNG-NAM
TAKE CARE OF LEFTOVERS
You can just give it to me. Thank you.
ZUHA AND SEONG-JUN DO THE DISHES
- Shall we talk to them?
- Sure.
Is everything okay?
Yes.
Today, in the morning…
- Yes?
- Why…
The gym…
No work out?
It's tiring.
"It's tiring."
Your Korean's so good.
It's gotten better from yesterday.
Right?
It's improving day by day.
It must be a survival instinct
because he has to
keep speaking Korean here.
Are you active in Japan these days?
Is that why you can still speak Japanese?
Not lately.
But last year in Japan, at an arena…
An arena tour?
It wasn't a tour.
I only did two performances.
BUT LAST YEAR IN JAPAN, AT AN ARENA…
"For three years, in Japan…"
- Arena? Arena tour?
- Yes.
"I was there"?
I only did two…
"I didn't forget."
A concert for fans.
"Concerts."
"Just a bit, so…"
HAVING A LISTENING TEST BY HIMSELF
Translate it.
- I'm studying right now.
- He's translating it.
They're too fast for me,
but I can hear you a little.
I try to be active in Japan every year
whenever I have the chance.
"Yattemasu."
"I was there"?
Let me go study for a bit. This won't do.
- All right, that was a great meal.
- Let's go.
KIAN'S B&B
Boss, didn't you say we'd open it?
Right, let's do it.
JUN-HO PREPARES TO OPEN THE KARAOKE ROOM
I'll turn the lights off.
There we go.
THE BOSS CHANGES INTO HIS SUIT
WASHES HIS FACE
AND TIDIES HIS HAIR
ONCE AGAIN
ALL EYES ON HIM
What?
You look clean-cut.
Isn't that the suit he wore
when he sang "Stay With Me"?
You look so cool.
You're a little too dolled up.
I only put water in my hair.
What are you talking about?
Everyone.
The opening
of Kian's B&B Karaoke begins now.
Please give a big round of applause.
KIAN'S B&B KARAOKE
First of all,
we want to give a huge thank you
to everyone who came here.
HOST LEE JUN-HO
There's someone
who put a lot of work into this night.
I'd like to introduce our boss, Mr. Kian.
Let's give him a big hand.
The final night has come at last.
Are you sad?
- Yes!
Well, that can't be helped though.
You all have to check out
and go back home tomorrow.
No!
To Kian's B&B,
she's our fairy.
Let me introduce Kazuha to the stage.
- They're going to sing a duet tonight.
- Really?
THE BOSS AND ZUHA'S DUET PERFORMANCE?
DURING AFTERNOON MEETING
I think we should go first
when we open the karaoke room.
You and Zuha wanted to do
a duet anyway, right?
- Are you okay with it?
- Yeah, I'm in.
THE BOSS AND ZUHA TEAM UP
What's your favorite song?
I was going to sing "Akai Sweet Pea."
"Akai…"
- "Sweet Pea."
- "Sweet…"
I've never heard of this song.
HE PRACTICED THE WHOLE TIME IN THE CAR
Everyone, how has your stay been?
- It's been great!
Were you happy?
- Yes!
You sure you won't forget this?
- We won't!
"AKAI SWEET PEA"
BY SEIKO MATSUDA
- We won't skip the intro.
- Okay.
HE MAKES AWKWARD GESTURES AGAIN
Why are you looking at me?
Look over there.
I thought you were doing something.
This is nice!
So nice!
Let's give them a hand here.
Let's do the wave.
The wave!
I'll gently snuggle up to your shirt
That smells of cigarettes
It's been…
STAMMERING
What was it?
ZUHA, HELP ME
Since we met
Why haven't you even held my hand?
ZUHA JOINS IN
With boots that have wings
I want to run through our youth with you
- Kazuha!
The flower buds by the railway are
Red sweet peas
I love you more
My goodness.
Than anyone I've met so far
I love your way of life
I can't go back like this
I can't go back
On the day spring came to my heart
There were red sweet peas
Good job!
Encore!
That was great.
What a beautiful night.
How nice.
BUMMED
I messed up a lot.
You were fine.
You sang it really well.
Great job.
- Was it okay?
- Yeah, you did well.
Yes, good job.
- I didn't know the lyrics.
- That was great!
- Seriously.
- That was great.
- That was so good.
- It was?
Boss, good job.
- Yeah?
- That's right.
Taro was grateful for the Japanese.
- I'm so happy.
- Really?
- I'm really happy. Thank you.
- So happy.
Shall we drink together?
Let's drink. Cheers.
WITH THEIR DUET PERFORMANCE
Cheers.
HAPPY KIAN'S B&B DAY BEGINS IN EARNEST
THEY SING IN THE KARAOKE ROOM
Cheers.
THE OTHERS BELOW HAVE FUN
IN THEIR OWN WAYS
It suddenly feels like a live music bar.
Isn't that what you wanted?
THE CASUAL VIBE THE BOSS WANTED
EXCITED
KARAOKE GOES ON WITHOUT ANY BREAKS
Bravo!
EVEN A SPECIAL BODYBUILDING PERFORMANCE
Way to go!
There you go!
HAPPY KIAN'S B&B DAY
GETS EVEN MORE EXCITING
HAPPY KIAN GETS EVEN MORE EXCITED
This is so nice.
Yeah.
You know, it's so nice
to see you feeling happy.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I hope he stays like this.
I can see how worried
you've been about this.
Yeah, I've been so…
- What is it?
- The karaoke…
Would it feel too forced?
KARAOKE WORRIED HIM
- I've lost a lot of confidence.
- Really?
Yeah.
I'm happy. But it's not just me, right?
- Cheers.
- Yeah.
Cheers.
- Incredible.
- Cheers.
MAXIMUM HAPPINESS
Let's sleep in tomorrow.
FLICK
Hey, this will be so sweet for you.
You have free time
until 11:00 a.m. tomorrow.
That's a sweet deal.
THEY DOUBT IT
If you want, you can go home
and come back by 11:00 a.m. tomorrow.
You can even fit in your own plans.
Do as you please.
You'll have plenty of time.
- Is free time until 11:00 a.m. okay?
- Sure.
FLICK
I thought you didn't see it.
Yeon-koung.
What is it?
I'm grateful
that you're following my lead.
All of a sudden?
I thought you'd want to be the leader.
What do you mean?
Since you've always been a leader
as a captain of a team or a coach.
I thought you'd look at me and think,
"This punk is a terrible leader."
But that person supports you.
She's so respectful.
Yes, sir.
"Yes, Boss."
Yeah, and she's like that
because you're the boss.
- But it always makes me nervous.
- Why?
Because I get worried
about letting you down.
Really?
SHE DIDN'T KNOW HOW HE FELT
It makes me work harder
to not be just an owner in name only.
Come on, she'd never think that.
- You're doing your best.
- Yeah.
- You're doing a good job.
- Right.
So if it gets hard for you,
I'll guide you.
Just follow my lead.
GLANCING
How have you been holding up?
I've become more comfortable now.
- You're okay?
- Because you try to put me at ease.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
- She does well on her own now.
- Yeah.
I like that you feel
comfortable around us.
- I like how friendly you are.
- Right.
THE BOSS IS GRATEFUL
THAT ZUHA ADJUSTED WELL
And I feel sorry to Jun-ho the most.
Why?
He has at least four Band-Aids
on his hands.
I saw him put some ointment on.
JUN-HO WAS ALWAYS WASHING DISHES
Let me use this too.
FIRST-AID KIT
You have blisters.
Is this all from dishwashing?
That and from taking care of the knives.
I got each cut while working.
No, it's not just me.
We've all gotten hurt.
Anyway, I'm the one leading you, but…
SAD
Are you going to cry?
- Are you?
- I will on the last day.
His shoulders…
HUNCHED SHOULDERS
Why are your shoulders hunched?
What's wrong?
This is why bosses always want
to have company dinners so much.
It's their chance to talk honestly.
What are you talking about?
This is when they can say
what they've been holding in.
I see.
Last drink.
Cheers.
12:50 A.M.
Everyone, it'll be lights-out at 1:00 a.m.
- Let's wrap it up.
- Okay.
Kian, is it okay to leave it like this?
Let's clean this up tomorrow morning.
Is anyone sleeping in the middle here?
No.
- Okay.
- No one.
THE KARAOKE ROOM CLOSES
THE BOSS TAKES OFF HIS SUIT
TV CABINET
NEXT TO THE RAMYEON BOXES
WINDOWSILL
FRIDGE
Good night.
Sleep tight.
THE STAFF GOES TO BED TOO
Good work, Kian.
Hey, get some sleep.
Okay.
IT'S DRIZZLING
DAY 6
9:00 A.M.
REMNANTS OF A BIZARRE MESS
ALL OVER THE PLACE
JUN-HO WAKES UP
STILL RETURNING TO REALITY
JUN-HO GOES TO WASH UP FIRST
YEON-KOUNG IS UP
Did you sleep well?
Yes, good morning.
WHILE EMPLOYEES WASH UP
Let's turn the lights on now.
SUDDEN FLASH
THE BOSS GETS UP
HE GOES TO WASH UP TOO
HE FINISHES SHOWERING
This will take forever to clean up.
11:00 A.M. CHECK-OUT TIME APPROACHES
We should clean it up then.
HIS GRAY SWEATSHIRT
THAT THE EMPLOYEES WASHED
CLEANUP BEGINS
CLEANUP LIST
CLEAR THE TRASH
Let's throw these away too.
Kian, open it up for me.
THE GUESTS HELP TOO
COLLECT FOOD WASTE
It's so fast when we do it together.
FOLD UP THE FURNITURE
RETURN TABLES AND CHAIRS
TO ORIGINAL PLACES
All done.
Let's go.
It's the staff's job,
but thank you so much for the help.
KIAN'S B&B HAS BECOME NEAT AND CLEAN
HE CLEANS HIS TEETH TOO
THINKING
HE PUTS IT IN THE BAG
AND A CLEAN SHAVE
GUESTS GET READY TO CHECK OUT
I'll pack my stuff first.
I was so glad a Japanese person was here.
- Really?
- I was relieved.
I worried no Japanese people
would be here.
Really?
I thought it'd be hard to communicate.
Thank you so much.
It was my pleasure.
It's time to check out now.
Say a few words, Boss.
When I first made this,
I thought guests would just be guests.
But now, it feels like
we become a sort of family.
So when you leave,
it makes me feel a bit sad.
I wish you happiness.
- Time to check out.
- Okay.
EVERYONE CHECKS OUT
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
See you again.
We'll get going.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
SIGHING
Hey, Jin-an. Don't cry.
I'm not crying.
Don't cry, okay?
Come on, don't do that!
All right. I'll open the door for you.
Bye, Taro.
- Bye, Yoo-min.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- Take care.
I'll be back with a medal.
- Bye.
- Goodbye.
Bye, Gi-pyo.
- Bye, Kian.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- Goodbye.
- Bye. Thank you.
ALL SEVEN GUESTS CHECK OUT
We're all leaving. This feels weird.
Man, all of us are leaving.
It feels as if we'll come back
later today.
It was fun.
As I expected, it was so fun.
Since my Korean isn't very good,
I thought it'd be hard to communicate.
Hello.
But they spoke to me in Japanese
and even in body language.
So I was really at ease during my stay.
To me, Kian's B&B is
"the perfect home."
Luge is a sport
that's unfamiliar to many people.
And they really wanted
to learn about the sport.
So as we told them about it,
I think it really boosted our confidence.
They cared for us and helped us so much.
I want to give them 200 stars.
When I was young,
I didn't really get to enjoy my childhood.
In children's homes,
around ten kids live together.
There's no personal space.
So I wished I could sleep alone
in a big room when I was young.
And it felt like
my childhood dream had come true.
For three days,
it was as if I got to enjoy
the life I had longed for as a child.
So I think Kian's B&B
is "a child's heart."
We'll get going.
Bye.
That was so fun.
11:10 A.M.
It's quiet.
So quiet.
Today,
we'll clean and organize.
We have time until 4:00 p.m. anyway.
So let's have free time to ourselves.
I think we really need it today.
We need a little time to ourselves.
Yeah, let's have free time.
I guess you've all hit the wall.
Now that it's the fifth day…
IT'S DAY 6
SHE GOT THE DAY WRONG
You're all exhausted.
I'm tired.
Is there anything you want to do
in your spare time?
What about food today?
- Food?
- What do we do?
- For lunch?
- For lunch.
Or we can order in.
We've never ordered lunch before.
- Right.
- Right?
IS IT OKAY?
Let's order in for lunch.
APPROVED
You pick what you want.
BRINGS FOOD DELIVERY BOOKLET
Pork cutlets, lunch boxes…
These look good.
Right. Osam bulgogi sounds good.
It does.
FOCUSED
- What do we eat? Bunsik?
- You want bunsik?
Hey, you know what? First…
Let's use up
all the leftover ingredients.
We have a lot of ingredients.
- Make something with them?
- With what we have?
Is there anything we can make?
Ramyeon. What else?
I'll make it really delicious.
FRUGAL OWNER
This looks good too.
CAN'T LET IT GO
- We can't order from here.
- This restaurant doesn't deliver.
You don't want ramyeon?
- We do.
- We'll eat it.
There are so many ingredients left.
We have to eat them.
BEGINS TO EMPTY THE FRIDGE
LEFTOVER INGREDIENT 1
CHEONGYANG CHILI PEPPERS
LEFTOVER INGREDIENT 2
BUTTON MUSHROOMS
LEFTOVER INGREDIENT 3
HOT PEPPER SAUCE TUNA
SCATTERING CRUMBS
FRUGAL
LEFTOVER INGREDIENT 4
RAMYEON
LAST INGREDIENT
4 EGGS
This looks good.
THE BOSS'S RAMYEON IS READY
Come and eat.
- Okay.
This looks good.
- It looks good.
- Gosh, Boss.
He made it for us.
We had a lot of ingredients.
Thank you.
- Enjoy.
- Bon appétit.
All right.
It looks so good.
- Seriously.
- It looks good.
What kind of ramyeon is this?
- Shin Ramyun.
- It's good.
Yeah.
INHALING
This is so good.
Ramyeon is the best.
You're really enjoying it.
Yeah, it's good.
SNIFFLING
It's a perfect hangover cure.
It's good.
In the end, we ate
what Boss wanted to eat,
not what Zuha wanted.
- Is that how it ended up?
- Yeah.
Zuha looked really hard
through the book to find what to eat.
TEASING
I looked really hard.
You say that after eating all your food?
FLUSTERED
It was good.
You should've told me clearly.
Like, "We're ordering in no matter what."
HUNCHED SHOULDERS AGAIN
- He's looking different from last night.
- Yeah.
He was confident and saying,
"Hey, you should've told me."
"Hey, I now know why bosses want
to have company dinners."
That's right!
"We have to talk honestly over drinks.
Right, Yeon-koung?"
- And he did speak honestly.
- Right.
I tend to change after 10:00 p.m.
We've figured you out now.
Really?
At around that time,
be careful.
I actually told Zuha too.
About what?
- "Hey, Zuha. It's 10:00 p.m. now."
- Right.
Yeah. "Avoid him."
She did tell me.
"We're next to Boss at 10:00 p.m."
- "Be careful."
- Right.
I like 10:00 p.m. the most.
Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
- It was so good.
Hey, has everything
been cleaned downstairs?
- Not yet.
- Right?
Then, I'll clean up the kitchen.
You clean downstairs.
Okay.
Or someone can help me wash dishes.
ASKING FOR HELP RIGHT AWAY
There's a lot to clean downstairs.
Really?
Honestly, there is a lot.
- Yeah, and we have to unfold the mat too.
- Right.
- We'll come up after we're done.
- Okay.
Come up when you're done.
Geez, my back.
- Let's dig deep and go clean.
- Let's do it.
Gosh, this will take forever.
LAST NIGHT'S PARTY AND TODAY'S LUNCH
RUBBING THOROUGHLY
RINSING THEM
LIKE A SPIN DRYER
SATISFIED
FINISHING UP WITH CLEAN WATER
- Let's tidy this up first.
- We should dust these off.
- Dust them?
- Yes.
There are so many.
So many comforters.
Let's do it.
Don't drop it.
- Ten times.
- Okay.
Ready, set, go.
10 TIMES IS THE OFFICIAL RULE
FOR SHAKING COMFORTERS
Five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten.
- Okay.
- All done.
Let's go in.
Let's go.
There are so many.
60 COMFORTER SHAKES LEFT
There's an endless amount of dust.
I think some got in my mouth.
Bon appétit.
Hey.
We're almost done.
What should we do with this?
We can't hang it, can we?
HANG IT HERE?
T-SHIRT COMFORTERS WERE HUNG ON HANGERS
BUT NOW
ONLY 2 ARE HANGING
You want to hang it?
They're all going to be new guests.
Because they're all new?
Let's try.
BUT…
Will it be possible?
THE HANGERS ARE ABOUT 3 M HIGH
Let's give it a try and not regret it.
- Let's do it.
But how should we do this?
If they made this sturdy enough,
it should be fine.
Can you hang it?
I can.
SUCCESSFULLY CLIMBS UP
It's going to be heavy though.
- I'll bring it over.
- Let me see.
I think I can do it.
Okay.
How heavy is this?
I think it's about 7 kg.
That's insane.
I can do it.
Okay.
ONE IS DONE
HANGS THE 2ND ONE IN NO TIME
Way to go.
Do the lightest ones.
Want to go up? I can lift you.
Try it.
- Here?
- Yeah, get on.
YEON-KOUNG TRIES TO LIFT
ZUHA ON HER SHOULDERS
Geez!
You must've eaten a lot of ramyeon.
- I can't go up.
- You got it?
- I can't.
- Why not?
Put your leg over the bar.
Wait. It's so slippery.
Hook your leg over the bar
and try to sit on it.
Hold on. Please take my sock off.
Your sock?
Damn it, where is it?
One, two, three.
Yes, that's it.
Oh, my gosh. Can you make it?
Okay!
- You got it.
- I got it!
- We did it.
- We got it.
- I'm seated.
- We did it.
The first step's done.
Now, you have to stand up.
You have to stand up.
Stand up.
CAN'T HELP BUT LAUGH
MOPPING
How did you get up there?
I lifted her up on my shoulders.
Be careful.
- That's it.
- Careful.
I can do this, right?
Okay, I'm up.
I'll bring a comforter.
You wanted to do this.
- I did?
- Yes.
RIGHT, I DID
Oh, no.
How did they hang these?
Hold on a second.
RIGHT IN
There you go.
- Very good.
- All right.
Yes, very good.
ONE IS DONE
- There you go. Very good.
- All right.
Gosh, that's amazing.
This is crazy. I'm really doing this.
That's it.
There you go.
Good job.
2ND ONE IS DONE
JUN-HO HANGS A 3RD
- Are we done?
- Come down.
Just let yourself go.
SHE GETS ON YEON-KOUNG AGAIN
WHEN COMING DOWN
- It's okay.
- Come on.
- I'll go slowly.
- Just come down.
I'm down.
Okay!
Thank you.
You're so light, Zuha.
We really did it. We're amazing.
We're amazing.
We somehow hung them up.
- You hung a lot up.
- We did it.
FROM TWO SHIRTS
TO SEVEN
- You hung five of them.
- Incredible.
Okay.
The laundry.
LAUNDRY BOX
THE BOSS TRIES TO LIFT THE LAUNDRY BOX UP
HE GETS A NEW HAT
Need help?
Yeah.
Why are you doing it alone?
Well, you seemed busy, so…
NICE CATCH
TUMBLES OUT
Sorry.
Geez.
I'll go up and take it from there.
You're just creating more work.
THE ONE WHO TAKES CARE OF SAID WORK
Lift it up.
Okay.
HE STARTS DOING LAUNDRY
There is a lot.
HE DOES IT ALONE TODAY
LATHERS THE CLOTHES WITH SOAP FIRST
SCRUBBING HARD
Gosh, my back.
Why is there so much?
GATHERING ALL HIS STRENGTH,
EVEN FROM HIS TOES
FINISHES LATHERING WITH SOAP
- Is there laundry left?
- I need to wring them.
ZUHA JOINS HIM
- Just wring them?
- Yes.
JUN-HO JOINS TOO
SQUEEZING DOWN
What's that? That's a new method.
Yeah.
KIAN-STYLE RINSING
This is an efficient way of rinsing.
That's not a bad idea.
She does it right away.
She learned immediately.
And she did it right away.
Hey!
Are you okay?
I'm going to lose my mind.
Hey!
I was so surprised.
You should've told me how to do it.
Try it again.
Wrap it around.
I used to do this in the military.
Hold it.
- I need to hold tight.
- Hold the top.
Yes, hold it
and squeeze down.
Yes.
Squeeze it down.
There you go.
I was so startled.
Squeeze it down. Yes.
- That's it.
- Nice.
Good.
- All right.
It's so funny how you're copying that.
Yes, squeeze all the way down.
Squeeze it.
- All right.
- Good.
- We truly belong at Kian's B&B now.
- Right.
We're all done.
All done.
IT'S FINALLY FINISHED
There's one more thing to wash.
- What?
What is this?
Isn't that new?
- Hey, smell it.
- Smell it.
JUDGING IT FROM THE SMELL
Is it okay?
Does it smell?
SHE ANSWERS WITH HER EXPRESSION
Should I say it's okay?
Just imagine that it smells nice.
Use all of your imagination.
You check it.
It's a pair of shorts?
It's new, right?
NO, IT'S NOT
DRYING IN THE SAUNA
Gosh, my back.
HE GOES UP THE SOFA WITH A RAG
AND OPENS THE WINDOW
Would cleaning the outside be too much?
What are you doing?
It's going to snow on Sunday.
I thought it'd be nice
if we could see the snow more clearly.
TO SEE MORE CLEARLY WHEN IT SNOWS
I can't believe I'm even cleaning this.
I'm so detailed.
It's perfect now.
It's so clean.
We're done.
We're ready to receive guests.
All set.
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
WORN OUT
Didn't you say
we'd have free time until 4:00 p.m.?
I did.
There's no time.
- She has to cook.
- I have to cook today.
I have to cook.
You have to cook right after cleaning.
TODAY'S MAIN CHEF
FEELING BAD
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
I apologize on his behalf.
Sorry won't cut it.
By the way,
when Mr. Lee arrived,
he said it didn't really feel
like they were welcomed.
- He was bummed?
- He said that's how he felt.
Right.
I'm really sorry,
but when you opened the door,
I think you should've welcomed us
with a big cheer.
It was a bit weak,
so more of a welcome would be nice.
DISAPPOINTING WELCOME
Really? We're sorry.
Our energy was too low.
SUGGESTION ACCEPTED
When new guests come today,
I think we should welcome them
in a more cheerful way.
Like, "Welcome!"
"Welcome to our B&B!"
SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
"Welcome!"
- "This is Kian's B&B!"
- "B&B!"
Like this.
"Please come in!"
Like a musical?
How should we do it?
When I open the door…
Once I open it,
and do this…
- "Welcome!"
EMBARRASSED
THAT'S NOT IT
Let's welcome them more passionately.
"Welcome!"
"Hey! Welcome!"
LIKE THIS
Do it like this and be all dramatic.
WELCOMING WITH HIS WHOLE BODY
In that case,
let's force ourselves to bring the energy.
When they knock on the door,
I'll speak in a singsong tone.
I'll try something.
BOSS WILL BEGIN BY SINGING
Then, you do a ballet jump.
You run and jump, like a crane.
- Sounds good.
- And?
What's next?
Then, you spike a volleyball.
I like that.
I'll hit it to a wall or wherever.
Then, Jun-ho
does something boyfriend-like.
Give out welcome drinks
- with a towel on your arm.
- Like this?
"Welcome."
- "Come on in."
- Exactly.
Yeah.
"Would you like a drink?"
"Do you need anything?"
- Sounds good.
- Yeah.
THEY FINISH PLANNING
Little by little, we're getting better.
- What?
- I'm getting a call.
- Hello?
I'm calling because we're checking in
to Kian's B&B today.
I see. Hello.
Where should we go and at what time?
I'll text you the address.
How many of you are there?
There are two of us.
- Two?
- Yes.
What time are they coming?
Check-in is at 4:00 p.m.
Are you going to come then? Or…
We'll try to get there at 4:00 p.m.
Okay, then.
Thank you. Bye.
- Thank you. Bye.
- Okay.
2 GUESTS WILL CHECK IN AT 4:00 P.M.
- Two guests.
- Yeah.
When will you start cooking?
When should I start?
Napolitan won't take long,
but Hamburg steak will take some time.
TONIGHT'S DINNER
NAPOLITAN & HAMBURG STEAK
I think you can start at 4:00 p.m.
- At 4:00 p.m.?
- Get some rest.
AFTER GUESTS CHECK IN?
3:00 P.M.
Rest with lights off?
That's not bad. Break time.
Let's take a break.
I think it'd be nice to have
at least one group activity per night.
You think so?
Or we just eat, drink beer…
ANOTHER MEETING INSTEAD OF RESTING
Go in the sauna and go to bed.
What should we do in the evening?
Any ideas?
- Games are too boring.
- Games?
That photo game was actually fun.
I bruised my knees.
I crawled around so much.
- She played so hard.
- You played the hardest.
I crawled so much.
How about hide-and-seek?
- There are a lot of places to hide.
- Right. That sounds good.
Good idea. Maybe with two seekers.
ONE OPTION IS HIDE-AND-SEEK
We should prepare two or three games.
What else?
If it gets boring, we should move on.
Right.
THINKING HARD
- Let's do that.
- What?
Give them food
and have them choose
an employee they'd like to eat with.
- Like a date?
- Have them stand behind the employee.
- And have a chat?
- Yes.
On reality dating shows,
they pick the people
they want to eat with.
Let's do that.
That's not a bad idea.
Do I need to get dressed up? What do I do?
What if you don't get picked?
Do you eat alone?
You have to eat alone.
That's so sad.
Honestly, you two are fine. Me too.
But he's never been picked.
Damn it.
- Why point that out?
- What?
Why point that out?
I've never been chosen yet.
Well, that's…
AVOIDING HIS EYES
But if a female guest comes,
you'll be chosen for sure.
Let's do it.
I'm sure they'll like it.
I think it's good.
IN ANY CASE, A GOOD IDEA
Our service is improving.
I'm getting a call.
What?
Are they here?
Hello?
We're checking in today.
We're Choi A-jin and Choi A-rin.
We'll send you the address.
You can come at 4:00 p.m.
At 4:00 p.m.? Okay.
Is the time okay with you?
It's totally fine!
Okay, make sure to come at 4:00 p.m.
- Okay.
- Okay, bye.
New guests.
- So, we have four guests coming today.
- Four so far.
TURNING LIGHTS BACK ON
Do we have to get up and work now?
No. I'm going to work out.
KIAN WANTS TO WORK OUT
What are you going to do?
I'm thinking.
Let's plan it out.
They're coming at 4:00 p.m., right?
Let's do about 30 minutes.
Let's do it.
- You two are working out together?
- Yeah.
Legs, abs, push-ups.
Are you okay with interval training?
You look so cool.
Just take your shirt off and do it.
I'll pump my chest up first.
Then, it'll look pretty good.
Let's go.
One, two.
- Nine, ten.
- Ten.
Two.
- Two.
- Three.
- Four.
- Five.
Five.
Seven.
Eight. Nine.
You're good with the 10 kg weights.
Ten.
Let's do it too. Let's do an ab exercise.
I'll follow your routine.
THEY START ZUHA'S AB WORKOUT ROUTINE
ZUHA'S AB WORKOUT ROUTINE IS INTENSE
There's no break.
Nope.
Ten.
KIAN'S GYM
Five.
We're getting a call!
- We're getting a call.
- Who is it?
Whose phone is it?
Another guest?
Hello?
- Hello?
- Hello.
- Another guest.
We're checking in,
but we don't have the address.
How many is in your party?
There are three of us.
I see. Then, I'll send you the address.
- Okay.
- And you can come at 4:00 p.m.
Okay, then.
It'll take a while.
It's a winding road.
I wonder what's at the end
of this winding road.
A HUGE AND STRANGE HOUSE
This is nice.
Six, five, four…
Three, two, one.
Okay.
- I think I'm done.
- I'm so tired.
EXHAUSTED
- I'm wiped.
- Me too.
So there are seven guests in total.
Groups of three, two, and two?
SEVEN WILL CHECK IN
- Let's get ready at 3:55 p.m.
- Okay.
You have to go all out and sing.
- What?
- Go all out and sing.
Go AWOL?
- You want me to run away?
- You said you'd sing.
- Oh, the singing?
- Yeah.
I thought you meant
like going AWOL in the military.
- I'll do it.
- We just need to do two more sets.
Thirty seconds and a 10-second break.
STILL WORKING OUT
THE BOSS WORKS OUT HIS ABS TOO
THUMPING
He's hitting his abs.
I've never seen that before.
A STRANGE, NEW AB WORKOUT
MODIFIED MOVES
THEY CAN'T WORK OUT
What kind of workout is that?
I'm so tired.
You're like a guest
on Ripley's Believe It or Not!
- What was that?
- What on earth was that?
- Boss, we'll hit your abs for you.
- What?
- We'll do it for you.
- We'll hit them.
We'll hit them for you.
Don't go too hard too fast.
Harder.
Go harder.
- Harder.
- You punk!
You're working me like a dog, you punk!
Look at how he's staying still.
STRESS RELIEVED
HEARING THE FUN, JUN-HO JOINS
I hit him hard, but he's okay.
Really?
- Help him.
- Don't go too hard at first.
Slowly go harder.
Are you crying?
It's sweat.
- With your heel.
- I'll stomp on you.
Zuha, I'll show you how to do it.
- Do it like this.
- Hey.
- Not too hard, okay?
- All right.
Are you ready?
GRUNTING
- Hey, I didn't do it properly.
- All right.
Zuha.
- I got scared.
- What on earth is this?
- I think fists will be better.
- Fists?
There you go!
NOW'S THE CHANCE
Zuha.
Put some power into it.
Got it, Zuha? Do it like this.
Like this, okay?
I'm getting endorphins from your turn.
I was going easy.
I felt intimidated by you though.
- You're done?
- Yeah, I'm done.
CREATING DISTANCE
It's more than enough.
HE HURRIEDLY WRAPS UP WORKOUT
Shouldn't we make some welcome drinks?
There's no time.
We have to do it now.
- We only have five minutes left.
- Really?
Zuha, is it 30 drops?
Yeah, 30 drops.
Seven guests.
ZUHA MAKES WELCOME DRINKS
Let's use this then.
HE BRINGS HIS PROPS
I can use this, right?
- The drinks on there?
- Yeah.
- Like this.
- Nice.
YEON-KOUNG ALSO GETS HER PROP READY
What are you doing with the ball again?
After Zuha does her jump and comes here…
SHE SHOWS UP WITH A VOLLEYBALL
Hey, it's already 4:00 p.m.
- What?
- It's already 4:00 p.m.
I'll walk in like this.
ALMOST CHECK-IN TIME
MEANWHILE, AT THE ENTRANCE
It looks so dreamlike.
Wait. Up close, it looks…
Can we open it?
It's Number 84, In-beom.
THEY KNOCK FIRST
Sir.
- They're here.
- Just a moment!
- Just a moment.
- To your positions.
- Okay.
Where is Boss going to show up?
You go behind there.
All right.
READY TO BALLET
Jun-ho, hurry up.
Hurry up.
WELCOME DRINKS ARE READY
VOLLEYBALL PERFORMANCE IS READY
EVERYONE ON STANDBY
Geez, singing…
Just a moment.
HESITANT
- Hello!
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you
- Likewise.
TAKEN ABACK
- It's an honor.
- Are you a group of two?
- Yes.
- All right.
He should be louder.
- Bring in your suitcases
- Thank you.
Two of our guests have arrived
Please, come on in!
Okay.
Nice to meet you!
DO WE NEED TO DO IT TOO?
CHECKING REACTION
Hello.
- Hello!
Hello!
Welcome, guys. Hi.
GLANCES
Hello.
Welcome to Kian's B&B.
Welcome.
- Have some welcome drinks.
- Wipe the suitcases with wet wipes
Bottoms up.
- Welcome!
KIAN'S B&B
I hear something.
It's…
What on earth?
It's so cold.
GETTING READY TO WELCOME NEXT GUESTS
Wait, do we have to jump up to open that?
It seems so.
Let's knock first.
- We do it again?
- They're here.
We have to do it again?
Should I spike the ball this time?
Don't you think so?
Come out right away.
- Okay.
- I'm embarrassed.
EVERYONE'S BUSY
If they're all hiding…
You can stay here.
This is so tough.
It's open.
Nice to meet you! Yeah!
Nice to meet you!
RUSHES OUT
You've come a long way
It's so nice to meet you.
HIS SINGING HAS IMPROVED
He's gotten better.
What?
It seems you're hikers
Gosh, he's having a hard time
closing the door.
When we go out, do we also…
Yes, open it that way when leaving too.
You can do that
ALMOST FORGOT
Is this some kind of rule here?
Here are our employees!
Hello, everyone.
HER TURNS ARE SMOOTHER NOW
Hello.
Hello!
- Hello.
SHE ADDS A SPIKE
BEWILDERED
Hello.
Hello, nice to meet you.
APPEARS RIGHT AFTER SPIKE
Welcome.
- Hello. These are your welcome drinks.
- Hello.
Nice to meet you!
Hello.
- Hello.
They're guests, not employees
- They're guests.
- Guests like you
- These are welcome drinks.
- Hello.
- Bottoms up.
- Thank you.
- What is this?
- So, this is…
We mixed lemon juice with water.
- It's a healthy drink. Yes.
- It tastes healthy.
- Drink up
It's delicious!
- Is it delicious?
- What is this reaction?
It's delicious!
Wait. Are we supposed to use this?
Take a look.
Sir.
More guests are here.
We have to do it again.
IT'S THE THIRD TIME NOW
Hold on. Could you move
to one side, please?
Sure.
Sorry, please go hide
We're sorry. We prepared this for today.
- We'd hoped you all came at once.
- We have to do it.
PLEASE HIDE
- Hello.
This is not easy.
Hide
What? What is it?
- Hello.
- Come on in!
Come on in!
- I was waiting for you!
- Hello!
- Hello.
- We were waiting!
SINGSONG MASTER
- Hello.
- Hello
Nice to meet you!
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you!
Let me introduce to you…
Our employees!
SLIPS
It's slippery.
SHE STILL FINISHES IT BEAUTIFULLY
Hello.
HER SPIKE HAS BECOME STRONGER
Volleyball, Kim Yeon-koung!
TIMES APPEARANCE PERFECTLY
- Hello, it's nice to meet you.
- Hello.
Jun-ho!
Here are your welcome drinks.
- Hello.
- Drink up
- Here's your welcome drink.
- Welcome!
KIAN'S BIZARRE B&B SEASON 2
Subtitle translation by: Wayne Ryu